Painterly Pack (Definitive Edition 1.10)
by rhodox


Unless noted otherwise, all graphics in this pack were edited and created by me. A few textures were generously provided by various individuals and are included in the pack with permission. These individuals are credited under their individual contributions on the web site (www.painterlypack.net). The default paintings are SNK sprites, and so belong to whoever made those games, I suppose.


This pack may be used in whole or in part by any owner of Minecraft, and combined with other texture packs, so long as credit is given and no profit or donations are solicited through that person's use of my textures and skins. You don't have to credit me if you use it with your youtube videos or promoting your server or things of that nature, but it's appreciated if you do.

The pack is given away freely (barring restrictions as noted on the Painterly website), however, donations for the time invested and ongoing development and testing of The Painterly Pack are extremely appreciated. The Donate link can be found on at painterlypack.net, and if you got it from anywhere else, it's not the official source and probably out of date. 
Installation Directions:
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
1. Go into the game, and click "Options" from the main menu.
2. Click "Resource Packs" from the menu that opens up, and then click "Open Resource Pack Folder".
3. Move this zip into the folder that opens when you clicked that button.
4. Select the Painterly Pack from the list of resource packs.
5. Enjoy!